{
    "subject": "King_Vidor",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Better_Times__1919_film_",
    "human_readable": "King Vidor directed the film Better Times (1919).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7731675505638123,
            "question": "What is King Vidor known for directing besides Better Times?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7197883725166321,
            "question": "Who directed the film Better Times?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6990540623664856,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by King Vidor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5886916518211365,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by King Vidor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5711832046508789,
            "question": "What year was the film Better Times released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5365571975708008,
            "question": "Was King Vidor a famous director during his time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4217929542064667,
            "question": "How influential was the film Better Times on later cinema?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42013874650001526,
            "question": "What genre is the film Better Times likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37744036316871643,
            "question": "What might be some common themes in films from 1919?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2793753743171692,
            "question": "Could you tell me more about the story of Better Times?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=King Vidor directed the film Better Times (1919).",
            "html": "yago_21649_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What might be some common themes in films from 1919?",
            "html": "yago_21649_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Better Times likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_21649_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How influential was the film Better Times on later cinema?",
            "html": "yago_21649_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21649_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21649_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21649_135.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21649_140.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21649_141.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21649_147.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21649_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21649_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21649_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21649_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents mention that King W. Vidor directed the film \"Better Times\" in 1919, which directly supports the statement that King Vidor directed the film \"Better Times (1919)\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}